[
    {
        "front": "あさ",
        "back": "朝 \nmorning",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょうしょく",
        "back": "朝食 \nmorning meal, breakfast",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "けさ",
        "back": "今朝 \nthis morning",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あさひ",
        "back": "朝日 \nmorning sun",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひる",
        "back": "昼 \nnoon",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうしょく",
        "back": "昼食 \nnoon meal, lunch",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひるやすみ",
        "back": "昼休み \nlunch break",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "よる",
        "back": "夜 \nnight",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんや",
        "back": "今夜 \ntonight",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "よみせ",
        "back": "夜店 \nnight stall",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "やしょく",
        "back": "夜食 \nbedtime snacks",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうがた",
        "back": "夕方 \nevening",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうしょく",
        "back": "夕食 \ndinner",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうひ",
        "back": "夕日 \nsunset, evening sun",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "たなばた",
        "back": "七夕 \nstar festival",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうがた",
        "back": "夕方 \nevening",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "あのかた",
        "back": "あの方 \nthat person",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほうほう",
        "back": "方法 \nmethod",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "よみかた",
        "back": "読み方 \nway to read",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "かきかた",
        "back": "書き方 \nthe way of writing",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばん",
        "back": "晩 \nevening",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばんごはん",
        "back": "晩ご飯 \ndinner",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいばん",
        "back": "毎晩 \nevery evening",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいかく",
        "back": "計画 \nplan",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "とけい",
        "back": "時計 \nwatch, clock",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "はかる",
        "back": "計る \nto measure",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごうけい",
        "back": "合計 \ntotal",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "にちようび",
        "back": "日曜日 \nsunday",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "げつようび",
        "back": "月曜日 \nmonday",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いじょう",
        "back": "以上 \nmore than, that's it",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いか",
        "back": "以下 \nless than",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いがい",
        "back": "以外 \nexcept for",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いぜん",
        "back": "以前 \npreviously",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんど",
        "back": "温度 \ntemperature",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんど",
        "back": "今度 \nnext time",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちど",
        "back": "一度 \nonce",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    },
    {
        "front": "～ど",
        "back": "～度 \ndegree celsius",
        "chapter": "N4 K10"
    }
]